D2.
Read Millie's article for Teenagers Magazine.
Practice makes perfect.
A year ago, when I wanted to share my ideas in an English class, I could not express myself well.
I felt sorry about that, so I made a plan to improve my English.
I listened to English on a language learning app every morning after I got up.
I also repeated the sentences to improve my pronunciation.
The app helped me correct my mistakes.
What's more, I practiced speaking English with my classmates at school.
Several months later, my English became much better and I was not afraid of speaking English anymore.
Practice makes perfect.
Now I am happy that I can express myself well in English.